<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="73">
    <title>
        <en>Tree Growth Manager</en>
        <de>Baumwachstumsmanager</de>
        <br>Gerente de Crescimento de Árvores</br>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[
Make forrestry on your farm more enjoyable and cost effective, by taking control of the amount of time it takes each species of tree to fully grow to maturity.
TGM gives you the ability to change the growth rate of a particular tree species from 100% up to 195% - or even down to 5% if you so desire.

TGM provides a custom settings menu, which can be accessed by the default keybind of LEFT ALT + 1. In a multiplayer setting, this menu will only be accessible by admins.

If you'd like to report a bug with this mod or would like to translate the mod into your own language, head on over to our <a href="https://github.com/Beaver-Bois-Modding/fs22-tgm">GitHub repository</a>.

Changelog 1.1.2.0:
- Added Brazilian Portuguese translation

Changelog 1.1.1.0:
- Updated icon
- Added German translation

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Implemented a custom settings menu, instead of extending the built-in game settings menu
- Fixed issues navigating the settings with a controller
- Fixed tree names not being loaded correctly for non-base maps (e.g. Silverrun Forest from the Platinum Expansion)
- Switched the axis of the growth rates to make it more intuitive (e.g. 105% is now faster and 95% is now slower, instead of the other way around)
- Implemented grouping of growth rates for variations of the same tree type
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[
Machen Sie die Forstwirtschaft auf Ihrer Farm angenehmer und kostengünstiger, indem Sie die Zeit kontrollieren, die jede Baumart benötigt, um vollständig zur Reife zu wachsen.
TGM gibt Ihnen die Möglichkeit, die Wachstumsrate einer bestimmten Baumart von 100 % auf 195 % zu ändern – oder sogar auf 5 %, wenn Sie dies wünschen.

TGM bietet ein benutzerdefiniertes Einstellungsmenü, auf das mit der Standardtastenkombination LINKS ALT + 1 zugegriffen werden kann. In einer Mehrspielereinstellung ist dieses Menü nur für Administratoren zugänglich.

Wenn Sie einen Fehler mit diesem Mod melden oder den Mod in Ihre eigene Sprache übersetzen möchten, besuchen Sie unser <a href="https://github.com/Beaver-Bois-Modding/fs22-tgm">GitHub-Repository</a>.

Änderungsprotokoll 1.1.2.0:
- Brasilianische portugiesische Übersetzung hinzugefügt

Änderungsprotokoll 1.1.1.0:
- Aktualisiertes Symbol
- Deutsche Übersetzung hinzugefügt

Änderungsprotokoll 1.1.0.0:
- Ein benutzerdefiniertes Einstellungsmenü implementiert, anstatt das integrierte Spieleinstellungsmenü zu erweitern
- Probleme beim Navigieren in den Einstellungen mit einem Controller behoben
- Behoben, dass Baumnamen für Nicht-Basiskarten nicht korrekt geladen wurden (z. B. Silverrun Forest aus der Platinum-Erweiterung)
- Achse der Wachstumsraten geändert, um es intuitiver zu machen (z. B. 105 % ist jetzt schneller und 95 % ist jetzt langsamer, anstatt umgekehrt)
- Implementierte Gruppierung von Wachstumsraten für Variationen des gleichen Baumtyps
]]>
        </de>
        <br>
<![CDATA[
Torne a silvicultura em sua fazenda mais agradável e econômica, controlando a quantidade de tempo que cada espécie de árvore leva para crescer totalmente até a maturidade.
O TGM oferece a capacidade de alterar a taxa de crescimento de uma determinada espécie de árvore de 100% até 195% - ou até 5%, se desejar.

O TGM fornece um menu de configurações personalizadas, que pode ser acessado pela combinação de teclas padrão de LEFT ALT + 1. Em uma configuração multijogador, este menu só será acessível por administradores.

Se você gostaria de relatar um bug com este mod ou gostaria de traduzir o mod para seu próprio idioma, acesse nosso <a href="https://github.com/Beaver-Bois-Modding/fs22-tgm">Repositório GitHub</a>.

Registro de alterações 1.1.2.0:
- Adicionada tradução para o português do Brasil

Registro de alterações 1.1.1.0:
- Ícone atualizado
- Adicionado tradução em alemão

Registro de alterações 1.1.0.0:
- Implementado um menu de configurações personalizadas, em vez de estender o menu de configurações do jogo integrado
- Correção de problemas ao navegar pelas configurações com um controlador
- Nomes de árvore corrigidos não sendo carregados corretamente para mapas não básicos (por exemplo, Silverrun Forest da expansão Platinum)
- Mudou o eixo das taxas de crescimento para torná-lo mais intuitivo (por exemplo, 105% agora é mais rápido e 95% agora é mais lento, em vez do contrário)
- Agrupamento implementado de taxas de crescimento para variações do mesmo tipo de árvore
]]>
        </br>
    </description>
    <version>1.1.2.0-dev</version>
    <author>Beaver Bois Modding</author>
    <iconFilename>icon_treeGrowthManager.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <l10n filenamePrefix="data/l10n/locale" />

    <actions>
        <action name="TGM_SHOW_SETTINGS" axisType="HALF" />
    </actions>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="TGM_SHOW_SETTINGS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_1" index="1" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
